Guide to the National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets 1945-1969
National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets
- NAM Publications (1 of 2), 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: The Interlocking Economies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Philip D. Reed. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Management and Labor- Their Common Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Matthew Woll. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: For a Better Tomorrow, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Earl Bunting. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Which Way to Peace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Spruille Braden. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industry is a Good Neighbor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By S.C. Allyn. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Management and Labor- Their Common Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Your Bulwark for Democracy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Paul G. Hoffman. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Teamwork Among Nations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NAM Publications (2 of 2), 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: What's Ahead in Labor-Management Relations?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By M.M. Anderson. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Unbeatable Partnership, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Spotlight on Job Security "The American Dream", Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Personnel is People, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Harry A. Bullis. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Personnel is People, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Conversation- Weapon Against Want, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By George M. Gadsby. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Public's Stake in Patents, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Howard E. Blood. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Government-Streamlined for Efficiency, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Clarence J. Brown. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bubonic Budgets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Lane D. Webber. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Capital- The Priceless Ingredient, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Joseph Morrell Dodge. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Economic Trends and the Outlook for Wages, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Dr. Leo Wolman. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1943-1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Capital Formation Under Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Public and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Management Answers to Some Union Objectinos on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Employee Benefit Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Industry Believes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Working Together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Effective Communication in Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Paul Pigors. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: The Public Be Served, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Statement of Managing Director, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Earl Bunting. November 15, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NAM Publications, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Business Size and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Views the National Labor Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Carroll E. French. 5/12/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Capital Formation Under Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Why Deficit Spending?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The Role of Government in our Economic Life, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Earl Bunting. 10/10/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Significance and Aftermath of the Steel Fact-Finding Panel, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Robert W. Stoddard. 12/9/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Is Bigness Bad in Business?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Raymond Moley. 12/9/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Where We Live, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Ralph W. Carney. 12/7/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Implications of Labor Monopoly in Industry-Wide Bargaining, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Theodore R. Iserman. 12/9/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Industrial Relations and a Free Enterprise Economy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Carroll E. French. 10/5/1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Employee Benefit Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NAM Publications, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: America's Labor Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Industry Looks at Its Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Earl Bunting. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Economic Impact of an Industry-wide Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Techniques of Securing Agreement in Job Evaluation Committees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Edward N. Hay. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Profits and Prices, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Faces the Pension Problem, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Water In Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Case Book Employee Communications in Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Multi-Employer Bargaining- Good or Bad?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Leo Teplow. 1/30/1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Federal Program of Old Age and Survivors Insurance and HR 6000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Meaning of Unemployment Statistics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Unemployment Estimates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Industry Looks At Its Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Earl Bunting. October 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Security lives in the heart.., Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NAM Publications, 1922-1927; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: National Association of Manufacturers Exposed, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Report of Committee on Open Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Class Legislation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Hon. Charles E. Littlefield. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Throttling the Nation's Press, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Class Legislation for Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 5/20/1908. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Free Men, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Wendell L. Willkie. 12/8/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Principles Behind Employer-Employee Harmony, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Charles R. Hook. 12/8/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Declaration of Principles Relating to the Conduct of American Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Public and a Program for Industrial Harmony, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By A.W. Hawkes. 12/8/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Government Finance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: The Catalyzers of Liberty, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By H.W. Prentis, Jr. 12/8/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Interstate Trade BarriersA Challenge to Our Economy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By R.W. Moore. 12/5/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Individual Enterprise: Our System Defined, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By William L. Batt. 12/5/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Patents and Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Robert L. Lund. 12/7/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Who Can Answer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Mrs. Carrie Chapman Catt. 12/8/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Open Shop Bulletin No.19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 8, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NAM Publications, 1922-1927; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Address of John Kirby, Jr., Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By John Kirby, Jr. 5/20/1913. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Reports of The Treasurer and The Secretary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 14-16, 1923. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Illegal Aspects of the "Sit-Down" Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Legislative Situation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By James A. Emery. May 20, 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Address of John Kirby, Jr., Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Reports of the Treasurer and the Secretary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Annual Address of President J.E. Edgerton, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 15, 1923. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Will the Five-Day Week Become Universal? It Will Not!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Building and the Public, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Employment Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: The Open Door, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Rev. S. Parkes Cadman. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: National Education and Employment Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 5, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Conditions in England, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Noel Sargent. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Evidence in the Case for the Open Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Employment Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: Immigration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1923. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Report of Committee on Open Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: Facts About Child Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: Open Shop Bulletin No. 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 29, 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Labor Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Staunton B. Peck. November 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Cost of Industrial Disputes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 22: A Practical Test of the Closed Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 23: The American Principle of Freedom in Employment Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- NAM Publications, 1914-1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Practical Test of the Closed Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Banker and the Open Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1923. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Open Shop Bulletin No. 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 22, 1921. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Evidence for the Open Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 28, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Closed vs. Open Shop Unionism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Open Shop Bulletin no. 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Industrial Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 15, 1916. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report of Committee on Health and Safety, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1917. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Old Age Pensions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Report of Committee on Union Label, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Uniform State Laws, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Report of Committee on Union Label, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1916. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Report of the Committee for Accident Prevention and Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Autocracy in Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Samuel Gompers. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Report of the Committee on Industrial Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 14, 1917. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Report of Committee on Industrial Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 25, 1915. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Platform for American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 18, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Digest of Workmen's Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 2,1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 3, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 2, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 4, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: From the Office of Rep. Charles E. Chamberlain, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: The Voice of NAM radio broadcasts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Transcript September 6, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: The Voice of NAM radio broadcasts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Transcript August 30, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: The Voice of NAM radio broadcasts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Emergency Strikes, Union Power & the Public Interest, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Investment Per Worker in Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: The Battle of Ideas, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Preserving the Management Function in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Information Bulletin May 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Your Future is What You Make It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- NAM Publications, 1914-1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Special Report on Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of the American Trade Commission on Industrial Conditions in Australasia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Preliminary Report of the Committee on Industrial Indemnity Insurance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Shake Hands With Tomorrow, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By C.M. Chester. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Workers Over 40, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Report of Committee on Patents, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: National Education and Employment Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Report of Committee on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Report of Committee on Taxation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Labor Organizations and the Sherman Act, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Chicago March 2, 1912. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Preliminary Report on the Legislative Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Industrial Betterment Activities, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- NAM Publications, 1908-1913; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Industrial Indemnity Insurance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 16-18th 1910. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Open Shop Bulletin No. 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, 1935-1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Bulletin Detail of New Social Security Act, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 12, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Some Notes on Employment Records, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 15, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 28, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 28, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 25, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 18, 1938. Item is in English.
- NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, 1939-1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Bulletin Supplement, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Collective Bargaining Management Obligations & Rights, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Special Labor Relations Bulletin Supplement on Labor Supply, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)